{
    "subject": "resource/Momtaz_Begum-Hossain",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/London",
    "human_readable": "Momtaz Begum-Hossain was born in London.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.97803795337677,
            "question": "Were there any significant historical events happening in London around the time Momtaz Begum-Hossain was born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9655441641807556,
            "question": "Where was Momtaz Begum-Hossain born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9650677442550659,
            "question": "Does Momtaz Begum-Hossain have any siblings or family members who were also born in London?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9443678259849548,
            "question": "What was life like for people living in London during the time of Momtaz Begum-Hossain's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9261493682861328,
            "question": "Is there a notable connection between Momtaz Begum-Hossain and London?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6710242033004761,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Momtaz Begum-Hossain?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.627686083316803,
            "question": "Is Momtaz Begum-Hossain known for anything specific?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24524542689323425,
            "question": "What country is London in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15899071097373962,
            "question": "What is London famous for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.11457274854183197,
            "question": "What are some interesting facts about London?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Momtaz Begum-Hossain was born in London.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7130_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is London famous for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7130_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What country is London in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7130_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Momtaz Begum-Hossain known for anything specific?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7130_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7130_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7130_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7130_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7130_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7130_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7130_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7130_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7130_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7130_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7130_66.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I found that:\n\n* The document with file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7130/re-ranker-msmarco/44.txt states \"Begum-Hossain was born and brought up in London, England.\"\n* Another document with file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7130/re-ranker-msmarco/17.txt also confirms \"Begum-Hossain was born and brought up in London, England.\"\n\nTherefore, the information supports the triple.\n\nResponse:\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents state that \"Begum-Hossain was born and brought up in London, England.\" Therefore, the information supports the statement that Momtaz Begum-Hossain was born in London."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}